app.highwire.com 2010-05-03

# Highwire Commerce - Privacy Policy

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES Highwire Commerce COLLECT AND WHY?

To provide you with the best service possible, we collect some or all of the following information:

  * your name
  * e-mail address
  * telphone number
  * shipping/billing address

When you use Highwire Commerce's services we track your activity on our website. Your personal information is used to identify you in our system allowing Highwire Commerce to interact with eBay on your behalf. We also track your Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name (if applicable), browser type, and request.cookies duration. Highwire Commerce uses this information to administer the site and to further improve our service to you.

If you elect to receive emails updates from Highwire Commerce, you will periodically receive e-mails from us updating you of significant events taking place at Highwire Commerce. You can always unsubscribe from this list by following the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in the e-mail correspondences.

## WITH WHOM DOES Highwire Commerce SHARE YOUR INFORMATION?

Please note that Highwire Commerce has links to other web sites. When you click on one of these links, you leave Highwire Commerce and go to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these sites, to which we link, as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## WHAT ARE "COOKIES" AND HOW ARE THEY USED?

A "cookie" is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Your browser must allow cookies in order for you to use the Highwire Commerce service. We use cookies to hold information, such as a login ID, so you don't need to re-enter information each time you utilize a Highwire Commerce service during a request.cookies. We also use cookies to provide customized and personalized services to you. Should you choose to set your browser to reject cookies, you will render it nearly impossible to use sites that set and use cookies, including Highwire Commerce.

## HOW CAN I REVIEW AND CHANGE MY INFORMATION AND CANCEL MY Highwire Commerce ACCOUNT?

You can edit and change your information in your Highwire Commerce account, including your password, at any time in the "preferences" section of the Highwire Commerce website. Should you forget your password, Highwire Commerce can send it to you immediately via e-mail, at your request. To cancel your account, you will need to submit a cancellation request from your store admin. We do not accept cancellations via support request or emails.

## HOW I WILL KNOW ABOUT CHANGES TO Highwire Commerce'S PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the "Start Page" of our site so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we shall notify users by way of this posting. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
